{
    "subject": "resource/Mattia_Lanzano",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Italian_footballers",
    "human_readable": "Mattia Lanzano's subject is Italian footballers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8145397901535034,
            "question": "Is Mattia Lanzano a famous footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.781102180480957,
            "question": "Who is Mattia Lanzano?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7630650997161865,
            "question": "Does Mattia Lanzano play football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7342265248298645,
            "question": "Where does Mattia Lanzano play football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6909825801849365,
            "question": "For which teams has Mattia Lanzano played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6648712754249573,
            "question": "What nationality are Italian footballers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.575671911239624,
            "question": "Is Mattia Lanzano known for his skills?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5712867975234985,
            "question": "What position does Mattia Lanzano play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4992976486682892,
            "question": "What is Mattia Lanzano's playing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25204941630363464,
            "question": "Has Mattia Lanzano won any trophies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mattia Lanzano's subject is Italian footballers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5410_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Mattia Lanzano's playing style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5410_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position does Mattia Lanzano play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5410_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mattia Lanzano known for his skills?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5410_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5410_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information about Mattia Lanzano, describing him as an Italian footballer. His career highlights and current activities align with the profession of a football player, supporting the triple that his subject is Italian footballers."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}